kidoor.com 2004-06-07

# EIN (Everyday Interactive Networks) - Help - Policies - Privacy Policy

****

**Reporting Abuse**

Please **contact us** to report abuse or violations of our privacy policy. We never knowingly share, trade or sell your contact information or any other information which you provide to us except in those cases where you decide to share your information with other users or partners online. 

**Email and Correspondence**

We may retain correspondence sent to us, electronic or otherwise. If you send us correspondence or others send us correspondence, or other members send us comments about your activities on this site, these are placed into a file made available only to authorized personnel and to you, when you are securely logged in to our server.

**User Profile**

At any time, you may view, update and/or remove your registered information once you have established your user profile. We believe that your information is your right to control. We believe communities must allow their members to continually decide if their personal information is to be available or not. We wish to lead the way in this regard. In the user's profile section, you can add or delete your personal information profile at anytime. On some of our sites, we may offer membership points for the more information you add in, so that you are rewarded for granting that information.

**IP (Internet Protocol) Address**

Every computer on the Internet has an IP address: that’s how our servers know where to send the web pages that you have requested through your browser. You may have a permanent IP address or your internet service provider may assign a random IP address each time you sign onto its servers. The IP address assigned to your computer reveals no personal information.  

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small amount of data that our server sends to your browser when you come to our site. Your browser transmits the cookie back to our server as part of its normal operation. Cookies are not “plug-ins,” contain no program code and they cannot access your hard drive. They cannot be used to spread viruses, etc. Cookies are identified with the web site which sent them to your browser and cannot be accessed by other web sites. Everyday Interactive Networks uses cookies to recognize you as a visitor or member of our service. This allows us to supply your browser with the personalized web pages that are integral to the easy use of our community site services. 

**  
Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

Prior to implementing any changes in our Privacy Policy, we will make these changes available to members and visitors through this page.   

**General**

Everyday Interactive Networks is very concerned about privacy and guards your data carefully. Everyday Interactive Networks may also utilize information about your visit in collective or aggregated data that does not identify you specifically. Our sites may collect some personally identifiable information about you. In the future, should Everyday Interactive Networks or any future owner of Everyday Interactive Networks decide to share our customers' transactional data with third parties, it will, in advance, provide notification and the opportunity for its users to indicate whether they would prefer the company not provide any identifiable information. Everyday Interactive Networks may occasionally send you information about our services. If you do not wish to receive this information, please flag the appropriate check box when registering for any personalized services. Additionally, internal practices help protect your privacy by limiting employee access to and use of customer data and encrypting customer passwords. If you choose not to register and provide personal information, you can still use most of our site. However, you will not be able to access areas that require registration.
